<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE xlingpaper PUBLIC "-//XMLmind//DTD XLingPap//EN"
"XLingPap.dtd">
<xlingpaper
version="2.8.0"
><styledPaper
><lingPaper
automaticallywrapinterlinears="yes"
version="2.10.0"
><frontMatter
><title
><object
type="tXLingPaper"
></object
> Quick Reference Guide</title
><subtitle
>using the <object
type="tXMLmind"
></object
> XML Editor</subtitle
><author
>H. Andrew Black</author
><date
>27 June 2016</date
><contents
></contents
></frontMatter
><section1
id="sIntro"
><secTitle
>Introduction</secTitle
><p
>This document lists a number of common tasks users often want to do when editing an <object
type="tXLingPaper"
></object
> document. Each task is given as a section or subsection. Look through the section titles in the table of contents or look in the <genericRef
gref="gIndex"
>index</genericRef
> and see if what you want to do is listed. If so, click on that section and then follow the instructions.</p
><p
>Some of the instructions refer to the Node Path Bar. Example <exampleRef
letter="xNodePathBar"
num="xNodePathBar"
></exampleRef
> points out where that is:</p
><example
num="xNodePathBar"
><chart
><img
src="resources/NodePathBarQRG.png"
></img
></chart
></example
></section1
><section1
id="sSaveAs"
><secTitle
>Save the file with a new name and/or in a new location</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iFileRename"
></indexedItem
><indexedItem
term="iSaveInNewLocation"
></indexedItem
>To save the file with a new name or to put the file in a new location, do this:</p
><ol
><li
>Use <object
type="tInstruction"
>File</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Save As...</object
></li
><li
>Change the file name in the “File name:” line, if needed.</li
><li
>Navigate to the new file location, if needed.</li
><li
>Click on the <object
type="tInstruction"
>Save</object
> button.</li
></ol
></section1
><section1
id="sOpenSection"
><secTitle
>Open a section or subsection</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iSectionOpen"
></indexedItem
><indexedItem
term="iOpenSection"
></indexedItem
>Sections are initially collapsed. To open one, click on the blue boxed plus sign <img
src="resources/BoxedPlusSign.png"
></img
> just to the left of the blue section number. This will open up the section.</p
><p
>Alternatively, you can click in the section title and then press the <object
type="tInstruction"
>Esc</object
> key (let it go) and then type the slash <object
type="tInstruction"
>/</object
> character.</p
></section1
><section1
id="sCloseSection"
><secTitle
>Close a section or subsection</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iSectionClose"
></indexedItem
><indexedItem
term="iCloseSection"
></indexedItem
>To close a section, click on the blue boxed minus sign just to the left of the blue section number.</p
><p
>Alternatively, you can click in a paragraph and then press the <object
type="tInstruction"
>Esc</object
> key (let it go) and then type the slash <object
type="tInstruction"
>/</object
> character.</p
></section1
><section1
id="sTable"
><secTitle
>Edit a table</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iTable"
></indexedItem
>There may be times when you need to modify the size of the table. The following subsections outline ways to do that.</p
><section2
id="sTableDeleteRow"
><secTitle
>Delete a row</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iTableDeleteRow"
></indexedItem
>If you need to delete a row in a table, do this:</p
><ol
><li
>Click in a table cell in the row.</li
><li
>Use <object
type="tInstruction"
>XLingPaper</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Table Row</object
> / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Delete</object
>.</li
></ol
></section2
><section2
id="sTableInsertRow"
><secTitle
>Insert a row</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iTableInsertRow"
></indexedItem
>If you need to insert a row in a table, do this:</p
><ol
><li
>Click in a table cell in the row before where you need to insert (if you need to insert a row at the beginning, click in a cell in the first row).</li
><li
>Use <object
type="tInstruction"
>XLingPaper</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Table Row</object
> / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Copy</object
>.</li
><li
>Use <object
type="tInstruction"
>XLingPaper</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Table Row</object
> / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Paste After</object
> (if you need to insert a row at the beginning, use <object
type="tInstruction"
>Paste Before</object
>).</li
><li
>Now edit the contents of each cell in the newly created row.</li
></ol
></section2
><section2
id="sTableDeleteColumn"
><secTitle
>Delete a column</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iTableDeleteColumn"
></indexedItem
>In the unlikely situation that you need to delete a column in a table, do this:</p
><ol
><li
>Click in a table cell in the column.</li
><li
>Use <object
type="tInstruction"
>XLingPaper</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Table Column</object
> / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Delete</object
>.</li
></ol
></section2
><section2
id="sTableInsertColumn"
><secTitle
>Insert a column</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iTableInsertColumn"
></indexedItem
>In the unlikely situation that you need to insert a column in a table, do this:</p
><ol
><li
>Click in a table cell in the column before where you need to insert (if you need to insert a column at the beginning, click in a cell in the first column).</li
><li
>Use <object
type="tInstruction"
>XLingPaper</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Table Column</object
> / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Copy</object
>.</li
><li
>Use <object
type="tInstruction"
>XLingPaper</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Table Column</object
> / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Paste After</object
> (if you need to insert a column at the beginning, use <object
type="tInstruction"
>Paste Before</object
>).</li
><li
>Now edit the contents of each cell in the newly created column.</li
></ol
></section2
><section2
id="sTableIncreaseSize"
><secTitle
>Quickly increase size of the table</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iTableChangeSize"
></indexedItem
>If you need to add many rows to a table, you can use the <object
type="tInstruction"
>XLingPaper</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Increase Table Size</object
> command. This brings up a dialog box where you can increase the number of non-header rows. (It does not work to decrease any of the sizes; it only works to increase the sizes.)</p
></section2
></section1
><section1
id="sInterlineat"
><secTitle
>Interlinear</secTitle
><section2
id="sInterlinearContent"
><secTitle
>Enter interlinear text content</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iInterlinear"
></indexedItem
>When you are creating an interlinear example, type in the correct content for each line. Use spaces between each word for any portion that needs to be aligned.</p
><p
>Finally, do what is discussed in section <sectionRef
sec="sConvertToWrd"
></sectionRef
>.</p
></section2
><section2
id="sConvertToWrd"
><secTitle
>Convert interlinear to special <object
type="tElement"
>wrd</object
> form</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iInterlinearConvert"
></indexedItem
>In order to make good use of glossing abbreviations in the morpheme gloss, we have to convert all the lines which need to be aligned in each interlinear to use a special format (called <object
type="tElement"
>wrd</object
> elements). This is even for those lines which do not have any glossing abbreviations in them. The idea is to overtly mark up each word that must be aligned in the interlinear with a <object
type="tElement"
>wrd</object
> element.</p
><p
>To do this,</p
><ol
><li
>Click in the example text you keyed (the first line).</li
><li
>Use <object
type="tInstruction"
>XLingPaper</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Convert interlinear line to wrd elements</object
> or hold the <object
type="tInstruction"
>Shift</object
> key down while pressing the <object
type="tInstruction"
>F10</object
> key. After converting, this will put the cursor at the beginning of the next line in the interlinear. Note that sometimes it takes a while before the cursor will move.</li
><li
>Repeat step 2 until you have converted all the lines that need to be aligned.</li
></ol
><p
><indexedItem
term="iAbbreviationAutoConvert"
></indexedItem
>As you do this, note that any morpheme glosses which match an abbreviation will automatically be converted to a special <object
type="tElement"
>abbrRef</object
> element. These have a yellowish background and show the abbreviation in small capital letters.</p
></section2
><section2
id="sInsertNewWrd"
><secTitle
>Add words to an interlinear</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iInterlinearAddNewWrd"
></indexedItem
><indexedItem
term="iAddWrdInInterlinear"
></indexedItem
>Sometimes, after you have already entered an entire interlinear example you realize that you need to add another word or two. To add a new word, do this:</p
><ol
><li
>In the first line, click in the word before where you want to add a new word (if you need to add a word at the beginning, click in the first word).</li
><li
>In the Node Path Bar (see example <exampleRef
letter="xNodePathBar"
num="xNodePathBar"
></exampleRef
>), click on “wrd”.</li
><li
>Copy (<object
type="tInstruction"
>Edit</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Copy</object
>).</li
><li
>Use <object
type="tInstruction"
>Edit</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Paste After</object
> (if you need to add a word at the beginning, use <object
type="tInstruction"
>Edit</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Paste Before</object
>).</li
><li
>Replace the copied word content with the new content.</li
><li
>Repeat steps 1-5 for each line that needs to be aligned.</li
></ol
></section2
><section2
id="sDeleteWrd"
><secTitle
>Delete a word in an interlinear</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iInterlinearDeleteNewWrd"
></indexedItem
><indexedItem
term="iDeleteWrdInInterlinear"
></indexedItem
>Sometimes, after you have already entered an entire interlinear example you realize that you need to delete a word or two. To delete a word in an interlilnear, do this:</p
><ol
><li
>In the first line, click in the word you want to delete.</li
><li
>In the Node Path Bar (see example <exampleRef
letter="xNodePathBar"
num="xNodePathBar"
></exampleRef
>), click on “wrd”.</li
><li
>Delete (<object
type="tInstruction"
>Edit</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Delete</object
>).</li
><li
>Repeat steps 1-3 for each line that needs to be aligned.</li
></ol
></section2
></section1
><section1
id="sAbbreviations"
><secTitle
>Abbreviations</secTitle
><section2
id="sGlossAbbrRef"
><secTitle
>Convert gloss text to use abbreviation(s)</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iAbbreviation"
></indexedItem
><indexedItem
term="iAbbreviationAutoConvert"
></indexedItem
>Sometimes you discover that a morpheme gloss did not get converted to an abbreviation when converting an interlinear to use <object
type="tElement"
>wrd</object
> elements. This is probably because of a typo or because the abbreviation is not in the list of abbreviations (see section <sectionRef
sec="sAddAbbreviation"
></sectionRef
>) or the spelling of the abbreviation in the list is not what you need (see section <sectionRef
sec="sCorrectAbbreviation"
></sectionRef
>). Other times, you may have a morpheme gloss with an abbreviation in a prose paragraph. How do you get these to convert to the correct <object
type="tElement"
>abbrRef</object
> element?</p
><p
>Do this:</p
><ol
><li
>Click in the abbreviation that needs to be converted.</li
><li
>Use <object
type="tInstruction"
>XLingPaper</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Convert any abbreviations in gloss to abbrRefs</object
> or hold the <object
type="tInstruction"
>Shift</object
> and <object
type="tInstruction"
>Ctrl</object
> keys down while pressing the <object
type="tInstruction"
>F10</object
> key. (You can also use the <object
type="tInstruction"
>XLingPaper</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Convert interlinear line to wrd elements</object
> or hold the <object
type="tInstruction"
>Shift</object
> key down while pressing the <object
type="tInstruction"
>F10</object
> key.)</li
></ol
></section2
><section2
id="sCorrectAbbreviation"
><secTitle
>Correct an abbreviation</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iAbbreviationCorrect"
></indexedItem
>Sometimes the abbreviation in the list of abbreviations is not the one you need to use. To correct it, do this:</p
><ol
><li
>Open up the second Abbreviations section (the first one is where the abbreviations used in your grammar will appear in the output). See section <sectionRef
sec="sOpenSection"
></sectionRef
> for how to open up a section.</li
><li
>Scan down the list of abbreviations until you find the place where your abbreviation is.</li
><li
>Click in the abbreviation and change it.</li
></ol
></section2
><section2
id="sAddAbbreviation"
><secTitle
>Add a new abbreviation</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iAbbreviationAdd"
></indexedItem
>Sometimes you find that an abbreviation you need is not in the list of abbreviations. To add a new one, do this:</p
><ol
><li
>Open up the second Abbreviations section (the first one is where the abbreviations used in your grammar will appear in the output). See section <sectionRef
sec="sOpenSection"
></sectionRef
> for how to open up a section.</li
><li
>Scan down the list of abbreviations until you find the place where your new abbreviation will alphabetize correctly.</li
><li
>Click on the yellow part of the abbreviation before it (if it's the first, click on the first one).</li
><li
>Copy (<object
type="tInstruction"
>Edit</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Copy</object
>.</li
><li
>Use <object
type="tInstruction"
>Edit</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Paste After</object
> (if you need to add an abbreviation at the beginning, use <object
type="tInstruction"
>Edit</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Paste Before</object
>).</li
><li
>Click in the yellow part, just after the v and type in a unique identifier (please note that this should use just a-z, A-Z, and number characters - no blanks and no punctuation and no accented or special characters). Replace the old one.</li
><li
>Click in the first part before the equals sign, type the abbreviation you need, replacing the old one.</li
><li
>Click in the part after the equals sign.</li
><li
>Type in the description of the abbreviation, replacing the old one.</li
></ol
></section2
></section1
><section1
id="sOutput"
><secTitle
>Output</secTitle
><section2
id="sProduceWebPage"
><secTitle
>Produce web page output</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iWebPageProduce"
></indexedItem
><indexedItem
term="iOutputWebPage"
></indexedItem
>To produce the web page output for your grammar, use <object
type="tInstruction"
>XLingPaper</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Produce Webpage</object
> or press the <object
type="tInstruction"
>F7</object
> key.</p
></section2
><section2
id="sSeeWebPage"
><secTitle
>See web page output</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iWebPageSee"
></indexedItem
><indexedItem
term="iOutputSeeWebPage"
></indexedItem
>To see the web page output for your grammar, use <object
type="tInstruction"
>XLingPaper</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Show Webpage</object
> or press the <object
type="tInstruction"
>F8</object
> key. This will show the web page in your browser. Note that if you already are viewing the web page in a browser, then you can reload (or refresh) the page in your browser after producing the web page again (see section <sectionRef
sec="sProduceWebPage"
></sectionRef
>).</p
></section2
><section2
id="sProducePDF"
><secTitle
>Produce PDF output</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iPDF"
></indexedItem
><indexedItem
term="iOutputPDF"
></indexedItem
>To produce the PDF output for your grammar, use <object
type="tInstruction"
>XLingPaper</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Produce PDF</object
> or press the <object
type="tInstruction"
>F9</object
> key.</p
></section2
></section1
><section1
id="sInsertingNewMaterial"
><secTitle
>Inserting new material</secTitle
><p
>This section is a reminder of how to insert a new paragraph, section, or interlinear example. Since <object
type="tXLingPaper"
></object
> uses a structured editor, the process for doing this is often different from what you may be used to. The following sections outline how to do that.</p
><section2
id="sInsertParagraph"
><secTitle
>Insert new paragraph</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iParagraph"
></indexedItem
><indexedItem
term="iInsertParagraph"
></indexedItem
>The key thing to keep in mind is that you need to “select” the structure after which (or before which) a paragraph can go. Do this:</p
><p
>If you are inserting a paragraph immediately after another paragraph, merely click at the end of the paragraph and press the <object
type="tInstruction"
>Enter</object
> key. This will start a new paragraph.</p
><p
>If, on the other hand, you want to insert a new paragraph after something like an example, do this:</p
><ol
><li
>Click in the material before which you want to insert the new paragraph.</li
><li
>In the Node Path Bar (see example <exampleRef
letter="xNodePathBar"
num="xNodePathBar"
></exampleRef
>), click on what comes immediately after the last “section” item (the section items have a number after them: 1-6 indicating the nesting depth of the section).</li
><li
>Use <object
type="tInstruction"
>Edit</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Insert After</object
> and choose “p” (for paragraph) in the Edit Tool (upper right hand corner).</li
><li
>Press the <object
type="tInstruction"
>Enter</object
> key.</li
></ol
></section2
><section2
id="sInsertSection"
><secTitle
>Insert a new section or subsection</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iSectionInsert"
></indexedItem
><indexedItem
term="iInsertSection"
></indexedItem
>With a program like Microsoft Word, to start a new section, you merely need to insert a new header style. Since <object
type="tXLingPaper"
></object
> is structured, that approach does not work. With <object
type="tXLingPaper"
></object
>, you need to consider the structure of the document.</p
><p
>If you want to insert a section at the same level as the current section you are editing, do this:</p
><ol
><li
>Click on the number in blue background of the current section.</li
><li
>Use <object
type="tInstruction"
>Edit</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Insert After</object
> and choose “section” in the Edit Tool (upper right hand corner). (Note that the word “section” will have a number after it which indicates the nesting level of this section.)</li
><li
>Press the <object
type="tInstruction"
>Enter</object
> key.</li
><li
>You'll see something that will look a bit like this: <img
src="resources/SectionNew.png"
></img
></li
><li
>Type the title of the section in the hash area.</li
><li
>Click in the blue section just after the “s” and enter a unique identification for this section. Use a-z, A-Z, and digits for this identification.</li
><li
>Open up the section (see section <sectionRef
sec="sOpenSection"
></sectionRef
>).</li
></ol
><p
>If you want to insert a subsection at the end of the current section, do this:</p
><ol
><li
>Click in the last part of the current section (the last paragraph, example, etc.).</li
><li
>In the Node Path Bar (see example <exampleRef
letter="xNodePathBar"
num="xNodePathBar"
></exampleRef
>), click on what comes immediately after the last “section” item (the section items have a number after them: 1-6 indicating the nesting depth of the section).</li
><li
>Use <object
type="tInstruction"
>Edit</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Insert After</object
> and choose “section” in the Edit Tool (upper right hand corner). (Note that the word “section” will have a number after it which indicates the nesting level of this section.)</li
><li
>Press the <object
type="tInstruction"
>Enter</object
> key.</li
><li
>You'll see something that will look a bit like this: <img
src="resources/Section2New.png"
></img
></li
><li
>Type the title of the section in the hash area.</li
><li
>Click in the blue section just after the “s” and enter a unique identification for this section. Use a-z, A-Z, and digits for this identification.</li
><li
>Open up the section (see section <sectionRef
sec="sOpenSection"
></sectionRef
>).</li
></ol
></section2
><section2
id="sInsertInterlinear"
><secTitle
>Insert a new interlinear example</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iInterlinearInsert"
></indexedItem
><indexedItem
term="iInsertInterlinear"
></indexedItem
>Sometimes you realize that you need to insert a new interlinear example. Do this:</p
><ol
><li
>Click in the material before which you want to insert the new interlinear example.</li
><li
>In the Node Path Bar (see example <exampleRef
letter="xNodePathBar"
num="xNodePathBar"
></exampleRef
>), click on what comes immediately after the last “section” item (the section items have a number after them: 1-6 indicating the nesting depth of the section).</li
><li
>Use <object
type="tInstruction"
>Edit</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Insert After</object
> and choose “<object
type="tItalic"
>example(interlinear_l_g_g_free)</object
>” (for example which is an interlinear that has a line for the language, two lines of gloss, and a free translation) in the Edit Tool (upper right hand corner). Or possibly <object
type="tItalic"
>example(listInterlinear_l_g_g_free)</object
> for a list of related interlinear examples.</li
><li
>Press the <object
type="tInstruction"
>Enter</object
> key.</li
><li
>Type your language data in the first line with a space between each word.</li
><li
>Type the word gloss in the second line.</li
><li
>Type the morpheme gloss in the third line.</li
><li
>Type the free translation in the fourth line.</li
><li
>See section <sectionRef
sec="sConvertToWrd"
></sectionRef
> for converting this to the special “wrd” format.</li
></ol
></section2
></section1
><section1
id="sReferences"
><secTitle
>Citations and References</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iCitation"
></indexedItem
><indexedItem
term="iReferenceMaterial"
></indexedItem
>For complete details on how to enter reference material and citations to reference material, see sections 4.5 “References” and 8 “Citations” in the <object
type="tXLingPaper"
></object
> User Documentation (see section <sectionRef
sec="sSeeUserDoc"
></sectionRef
> for how to get this documentation). This documentation is currently only available in English.</p
></section1
><section1
id="sSeeUserDoc"
><secTitle
>See the <object
type="tXLingPaper"
></object
> user documentation</secTitle
><p
><indexedItem
term="iXLingPaperDcoumentation"
></indexedItem
><indexedItem
term="iDocumentation"
></indexedItem
>To see the <object
type="tXLingPaper"
></object
> user documentation, use <object
type="tInstruction"
>XLingPaper</object
> menu item / <object
type="tInstruction"
>Show XLingPaper User Documentation</object
>.</p
></section1
><backMatter
><endnotes
></endnotes
><references
></references
><index
><p
><genericTarget
id="gIndex"
></genericTarget
></p
></index
></backMatter
><languages
><language
id="lVernacular"
name="vernacular"
></language
><language
color="#446688"
id="lGloss"
name="gloss"
></language
><language
id="en"
></language
></languages
><types
><comment
>The following types are provided as pre-set examples. You may well want to create your own types that refer to one or more of these. You do that by typing in the names of the types in the types attribute of your type.</comment
><type
font-weight="bold"
id="tBold"
></type
><type
font-style="italic"
font-weight="bold"
id="tBoldItalic"
></type
><type
font-weight="bold"
id="tEmphasis"
></type
><type
id="tGrammaticalGloss"
types="tSmallCaps"
></type
><type
font-style="italic"
id="tItalic"
></type
><type
cssSpecial="text-decoration:none"
id="tNoOverline"
xsl-foSpecial="text-decoration=&quot;no-overline&quot;"
></type
><type
font-variant="normal"
id="tNoSmallCaps"
></type
><type
cssSpecial="text-decoration:none"
id="tNoStrikethrough"
xsl-foSpecial="text-decoration=&quot;no-line-through&quot;"
></type
><type
cssSpecial="text-decoration:none"
id="tNoUnderline"
xsl-foSpecial="text-decoration=&quot;no-underline&quot;"
></type
><type
cssSpecial="text-decoration:overline"
id="tOverline"
xsl-foSpecial="text-decoration=&quot;overline&quot;"
></type
><type
font-style="normal"
font-variant="normal"
font-weight="normal"
id="tRegular"
></type
><type
font-family="Charis SIL CompactSmallCaps"
id="tSmallCaps"
></type
><type
XeLaTeXSpecial="line-through"
cssSpecial="text-decoration:line-through"
id="tStrikethrough"
xsl-foSpecial="text-decoration=&quot;line-through&quot;"
></type
><type
XeLaTeXSpecial="subscript"
cssSpecial="vertical-align:sub;"
font-size="65%"
id="tSubscript"
xsl-foSpecial="baseline-shift='sub'"
></type
><type
XeLaTeXSpecial="superscript"
cssSpecial="vertical-align:super;"
font-size="65%"
id="tSuperscript"
xsl-foSpecial="baseline-shift='super'"
></type
><type
XeLaTeXSpecial="underline"
cssSpecial="text-decoration:underline"
id="tUnderline"
xsl-foSpecial="text-decoration=&quot;underline&quot;"
></type
><comment
>Add your custom types here.</comment
><type
color="red"
font-weight="bold"
id="tComment"
></type
><type
color="maroon"
font-family="Courier New"
font-size="90%"
id="tElement"
></type
><type
color="maroon"
id="tInstruction"
></type
><type
before="PAWS Starter Kit"
id="tPAWS"
></type
><type
before="XLingPaper"
id="tXLingPaper"
></type
><type
before="XMLmind"
id="tXMLmind"
></type
></types
><indexTerms
><indexTerm
id="iAbbreviation"
><term
>Abbreviation</term
><indexTerms
><indexTerm
id="iAbbreviationAdd"
><term
>Add a new abbreviation</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iAbbreviationAutoConvert"
><term
>Automatic conversion to <object
type="tElement"
>abbrRef</object
> element</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iAbbreviationCorrect"
><term
>Correct abbreviation</term
></indexTerm
></indexTerms
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iAddWrdInInterlinear"
><term
>Add a word in an interlinear</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iCitation"
><term
>Citation</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iCloseSection"
><term
>Close a section</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iDeleteWrdInInterlinear"
><term
>Delete a word in an interlinear</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iDocumentation"
><term
>Documentation</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iENTER..."
><term
>ENTER...</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iFile"
><term
>File</term
><indexTerms
><indexTerm
id="iFileRename"
><term
>Rename</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iSaveInNewLocation"
><term
>Save in new location</term
></indexTerm
></indexTerms
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iInsert"
><term
>Insert</term
><indexTerms
><indexTerm
id="iInsertInterlinear"
><term
>Interlinear example</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iInsertParagraph"
><term
>Paragraph</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iInsertSection"
><term
>Section</term
></indexTerm
></indexTerms
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iInterlinear"
><term
>Interlinear</term
><indexTerms
><indexTerm
id="iInterlinearAddNewWrd"
><term
>Add a new word</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iInterlinearConvert"
><term
>Convert to <object
type="tElement"
>wrd</object
> elements</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iInterlinearDeleteNewWrd"
><term
>Delete a word</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iInterlinearInsert"
><term
>Insert a new interlinear example</term
></indexTerm
></indexTerms
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iOpenSection"
><term
>Open a section</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iOutput"
><term
>Output</term
><indexTerms
><indexTerm
id="iOutputPDF"
><term
>Produce PDF</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iOutputWebPage"
><term
>Produce Web page</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iOutputSeeWebPage"
><term
>See web page</term
></indexTerm
></indexTerms
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iParagraph"
><term
>Paragraph, insert a new</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iPDF"
><term
>PDF output</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iReferenceMaterial"
><term
>Reference material</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iRemovetComment"
><term
>Remove tComment item with red text</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iReplaceENTER..."
><term
>Replace ENTER... with content</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iSection"
><term
>Section</term
><indexTerms
><indexTerm
id="iSectionClose"
><term
>Close</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iSectionInsert"
><term
>Insert a new section</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iSectionOpen"
><term
>Open</term
></indexTerm
></indexTerms
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iTable"
><term
>Table</term
><indexTerms
><indexTerm
id="iTableChangeSize"
><term
>Change size</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iTableDeleteColumn"
><term
>Delete column</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iTableDeleteRow"
><term
>Delete row</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iTableInsertColumn"
><term
>Insert column</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iTableInsertRow"
><term
>Insert row</term
></indexTerm
></indexTerms
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="itComment"
><term
>tComment item with red text, how to delete it</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iWebPage"
><term
>Web page output</term
><indexTerms
><indexTerm
id="iWebPageProduce"
><term
>Produce</term
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iWebPageSee"
><term
>See or show</term
></indexTerm
></indexTerms
></indexTerm
><indexTerm
id="iXLingPaperDcoumentation"
><term
>XLingPaper documentation</term
></indexTerm
></indexTerms
><contentControl
><contentTypes
><contentType
id="ctPAWS"
>PAWS output specific</contentType
></contentTypes
><contentControlChoices
><contentControlChoice
active="no"
>PAWS output</contentControlChoice
><contentControlChoice
active="yes"
exclude="ctPAWS"
>General</contentControlChoice
></contentControlChoices
></contentControl
></lingPaper
><xi:include
href="QuickReferenceGuideStyleSheet.xml"
xpointer="element(/1)"
xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
></xi:include
></styledPaper
></xlingpaper
>
